<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prostitution information center on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/tags/prostitution-information-center/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prostitution information center on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/tags/prostitution-information-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Sunny, sex worker in Amsterdam: let me explain you my world</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-en/</guid>
      <description>Italian Translation
 Sunny is a sex worker in Amsterdam. You will sometimes find her at the Prostitution Information Center, sitting on Enge Kerksteeg 3, ready to answer all your questions over a steaming mint tea waiting to be served. The Center is very beautifully decorated, pictures and posters adorne its walls, and towards the back is a spacious wooden table. People often take pictures from outside, but when someone tried doing so during our interview Sunny rushed to the window and waved her arms in disapproval, “we don’t want people to just take pictures, we want them to come in for a chat”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Io, sex worker al Red Light di Amsterdam, vi racconto il mio mondo</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-it/</guid>
      <description>Tradotto dall’inglese
 Sunny è una sex worker. Lavora al Centro di Informazioni sulla Prostituzione (Prostitution Information Center) a Enge Kerksteeg n°3, pronta a rispondere a tutte le vostre domande seduta davanti a una bollente tazza di tè. Il Centro è ben arredato, foto e poster decorano i suoi interni e, nella parte posteriore, è posizionato un grande tavolo di legno. Le persone spesso scattano le foto dall’esterno ma, quando qualcuno lo ha fatto durante la nostra intervista, Sunny si è subito precipitata alla finestra, agitava la mano in segno di disapprovazione, “non vogliamo che la gente scatti solo foto, ma che entri per fare una chiacchierata.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>