<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tessel ten Zweege on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/tags/tessel-ten-zweege/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tessel ten Zweege on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/tags/tessel-ten-zweege/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Printed and rebel, Amsterdam’s zine scene survives hipsters and tourists</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-en/</guid>
      <description>Photo via: Wikimedia, Author Lindsay Eyink, Licence CC BY 2.0
Wikimedia&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Author: W &amp;nbsp; CC BY 2.0 Lindsay Eyink&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Licence&amp;nbsp; --  Who would ever expect to find an anarchist bookshop in Jodenbreestraat Street, one of the most touristic spots of the capital? And yet there stands Fort of Sjakoo, one of the eldest stores of its kind, packed with shelves full of anarchist, feminist and left-wing political publications; the thoughts of some of the most important thinkers of history lay in ancient books, waiting to be read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ribelli e stampate: le zine di Amsterdam sopravvivono a hipster e turisti</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-it/</guid>
      <description>Photo via: Wikimedia, Author Lindsay Eyink, Licence CC BY 2.0
Tradotto dall’inglese
 Chi si aspetterebbe mai di trovare una libreria anarchica in Jodenbreestraat Street, uno dei luoghi più turistici della capitale? Eppure Fort of Sjakoo, uno dei negozi più grandi e longevi del suo genere, pieno di scaffali pieni di pubblicazioni politiche anarchiche, femministe e di sinistra è proprio lì.
 Per i dieci volontari che gestiscono la libreria è una missione quella di fornire un rifugio sicuro per riviste, cortometraggi indipendenti e autoprodotti, fuori dai circuiti.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>