<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lockdown creatives: Amsterdam’s Art in Times of Crisis</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-19-lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-19-lockdown/</guid>
      <description>In the past few months we have seen stuff we have never before and those drastic changes that Covid crisis brought with it has been difficult for many, such as Amsterdam’s artists who were forced to find new ways to create their art and gain inspiration.
 We can think back to the age of the bubonic plague, how it changed the lives of millions of people and it turned outbreaks into a recurring part of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OT301, the non-commercial community in the heart of gentrified Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-14-ot301/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-14-ot301/</guid>
      <description>OT301 is a cultural hotspot in Amsterdam. Questioning its narrative as an autonomous space; we tried to engage with OT301’s history and the current state of affairs.
 Back in the ’80s, the lack of affordable housing helped the squatting movement to emerge in the Netherlands. ‘Squatting’ is what most would describe as occupying, living, in an abandoned building; not just out of necessity, but as a conscious political act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taste Before You Waste, soul food in Amsterdam Oost</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-02-taste-before-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-02-taste-before-en/</guid>
      <description>Photo Credits: Taste Before You Waste
The coronavirus pandemic will bring an additional 130 million people to starvation, the UN warned in late April. Meanwhile, Europe and the United States are producing unprecedented amounts of food waste following the abrupt decline in demand from restaurants, catering services and school mensas. The message here is that the food system in the western world is ridiculously toxic and wasteful. While others starve, “over 1/3 of all food produced globally is thrown away and in countries like the US, 50% of the food produced is wasted,” explains Isabel Allen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Rebellion to Pandam: Covid is not a “blessing” for the environment. The future of the planet is still in our hands</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-04-28-extinction-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-04-28-extinction-en/</guid>
      <description>Photo credits: Sam ten Thij en Teresa, Extinction Rebellion NL
 As the world slowly takes its first steps out of lockdown one aspect is becoming increasingly clear: we need to re-think our social interactions, the way we will manage our environment in the future, and above all the way we define human values. The current COVID-19 crisis might offer a unique perspective to learn from. The current debate seems to focus around how we can regain the status quo and return to our old lifestyle – “once all of this will be over“.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes to consent, no to sexual violence: this is OBOV mission</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-04-19-yes-to-consent-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-04-19-yes-to-consent-en/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of the coronavirus crisis, a lockdown seemed extreme. Yet, over 100 countries implemented either a full or partial lockdown by the end of March. With the quarantine lasting weeks, people all over the world are forced to cope with a disruptive shift in their lifestyle. Working from home, the lack of social interaction, and the distressing uncertainty about the future. Besides these consequences, cases of domestic violence have surged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus and democracy, what do Amsterdam students think of the ongoing social crisis?</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-04-11-coronavirus-and-democracy-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-04-11-coronavirus-and-democracy-en/</guid>
      <description>Wrapping your head around the biggest world crisis since WWII is not an easy task: there is so much uncertainty, there are so many questions, so much instability. Spring is finally creeping into the canals and the parks of Amsterdam but for this year we can forget the drinks and barbecues with friends, the ease and joy of the first days of warmth. Something as small and invisible as a virus has changed our life: what should we think about it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racism, ripoffs and ruthless landlords: housing market in Amsterdam is a nightmare</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-21-racism-ripoff-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-21-racism-ripoff-en/</guid>
      <description>Numbers released by Statistics Netherlands revealed that, in 2018, the number of foreigners who registered at a Dutch municipality exceeded the number of people who left by 69.5 thousand. In 2018, between January and March, 186 thousand immigrants moved to the Netherlands; 4.5k more than during the same period in 2017. Amsterdam is known to be a truly liberal city, tolerant, welcoming and with a high quality of life, which is why the number of foreigners settling here is not likely to decrease anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catcalls of Amsterdam, marking sexism on the ground</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-07-catcalls-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-07-catcalls-en/</guid>
      <description>Since I started ‘Cat Calls of Amsterdam’ I developed this sixth sense: every time someone is about to catcall me or my friend, or just a random stranger, a radar goes off in me“ says Ambrien Moenrialam, founder of the Instagram site ‘Cat Calls of Amsterdam’. Together with her team of three, she collects messages people send her of their cat calling experiences. They then visit the place where it happened and chalk the messages on the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social and diverse: Oscam in ZuidOost is the culturale beating heart of Bijlmer</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-29-social-and-diverse-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-29-social-and-diverse-en/</guid>
      <description>When thinking about art and museums in Amsterdam, Museumsplein - located in the middle of the city center - is the first place that comes to mind. Or, for the more local sort, Jordaan and its variety of bohemian galleries offers a selection of fine art and sculptures. But rarely does Amsterdam South East, Zuid Oost, Watergrafsmeer blurring into Bijlmer blurring into Diemen, spring to mind.
 OSCAM, the Open Space Contemporary Art Museum, is trying to change this image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printed and rebel, Amsterdam’s zine scene survives hipsters and tourists</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-en/</guid>
      <description>Photo via: Wikimedia, Author Lindsay Eyink, Licence CC BY 2.0
Wikimedia&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Author: W &amp;nbsp; CC BY 2.0 Lindsay Eyink&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Licence&amp;nbsp; --  Who would ever expect to find an anarchist bookshop in Jodenbreestraat Street, one of the most touristic spots of the capital? And yet there stands Fort of Sjakoo, one of the eldest stores of its kind, packed with shelves full of anarchist, feminist and left-wing political publications; the thoughts of some of the most important thinkers of history lay in ancient books, waiting to be read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free contraception lawsuit: the pill is a women’s right, that’s why we sue the Dutch government</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-15-free-contraception-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-15-free-contraception-en/</guid>
      <description>Pic credit: Robin Butter
 In 1972 -following an intense campaign from the Dutch feminist group Dolle Mina- the Netherlands declared contraception free for all. Yesterday, on Valentine, “the day of love”, Dutch women are experiencing a déjà vu: feminist legal firm Bureau Clara Wichmann and NGO De Goede Zaak handed over a subpoena demanding free contraception for all to the high council in Amsterdam.
 PanDam spoke to Femke Zeven, spokesperson for Bureau Clara Wichmann: “It was really nice to be at the High Council with all of the organizations and individuals that together are also supporting the case as a group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam through stories, pictures and podcasts: this is Pan-Dam</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-07-amsterdam-through-stories-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-07-amsterdam-through-stories-en/</guid>
      <description>Pan-Dam was born in 2019, on the 22nd of October, in the cafè of the Kriterion Filmtheatre. A few weeks before I had decided to open my own publication, to break my inertia and finally get started on a project I had been fantasizing about for years. I spent sleepless nights posting and posting in a multitude of writing-related Facebook groups, texting and emailing hundreds of people, hoping to find someone willing to embark on this project with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Sunny, sex worker in Amsterdam: let me explain you my world</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-en/</guid>
      <description>Sunny is a sex worker in Amsterdam. You will sometimes find her at the Prostitution Information Center, sitting on Enge Kerksteeg 3, ready to answer all your questions over a steaming mint tea waiting to be served. The Center is very beautifully decorated, pictures and posters adorne its walls, and towards the back is a spacious wooden table. People often take pictures from outside, but when someone tried doing so during our interview Sunny rushed to the window and waved her arms in disapproval, “we don’t want people to just take pictures, we want them to come in for a chat”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>