<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amsterdam on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/tags/amsterdam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amsterdam on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/tags/amsterdam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam attraverso storie, immagini, podcast: arriva Pan-Dam</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-amsterdam-through-stories-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-amsterdam-through-stories-it/</guid>
      <description>Tradotto dall’inglese
 Pan-Dam è nato nel 2019, il 22 ottobre precisamente, nel bar del cinema Kriterion ad Amsterdam. Alcune settimane prima avevo deciso di iniziare a scrivere il mio articolo, dopo tanti tentennamenti, finalmente, è venuto al mondo il progetto su cui avevo fantasticato per anni.
 Ho passato notti insonni pubblicando centinaia di post su gruppi Facebook inerenti alla scrittura e stavo solo aspettando che tutto si allineasse perchè il sogno di scrivere ed essere letta, potesse diventare realtà.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam through stories, pictures and podcasts: this is Pan-Dam</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-amsterdam-through-stories-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-amsterdam-through-stories-en/</guid>
      <description>Link to Italian Translation
 Pan-Dam was born in 2019, on the 22nd of October, in the cafè of the Kriterion Filmtheatre. A few weeks before I had decided to open my own publication, to break my inertia and finally get started on a project I had been fantasizing about for years. I spent sleepless nights posting and posting in a multitude of writing-related Facebook groups, texting and emailing hundreds of people, hoping to find someone willing to embark on this project with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Sunny, sex worker in Amsterdam: let me explain you my world</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-en/</guid>
      <description>Italian Translation
 Sunny is a sex worker in Amsterdam. You will sometimes find her at the Prostitution Information Center, sitting on Enge Kerksteeg 3, ready to answer all your questions over a steaming mint tea waiting to be served. The Center is very beautifully decorated, pictures and posters adorne its walls, and towards the back is a spacious wooden table. People often take pictures from outside, but when someone tried doing so during our interview Sunny rushed to the window and waved her arms in disapproval, “we don’t want people to just take pictures, we want them to come in for a chat”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Io, sex worker al Red Light di Amsterdam, vi racconto il mio mondo</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/public/posts/2020-02-07-i-am-sunny-it/</guid>
      <description>Tradotto dall’inglese
 Sunny è una sex worker. Lavora al Centro di Informazioni sulla Prostituzione (Prostitution Information Center) a Enge Kerksteeg n°3, pronta a rispondere a tutte le vostre domande seduta davanti a una bollente tazza di tè. Il Centro è ben arredato, foto e poster decorano i suoi interni e, nella parte posteriore, è posizionato un grande tavolo di legno. Le persone spesso scattano le foto dall’esterno ma, quando qualcuno lo ha fatto durante la nostra intervista, Sunny si è subito precipitata alla finestra, agitava la mano in segno di disapprovazione, “non vogliamo che la gente scatti solo foto, ma che entri per fare una chiacchierata.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>