<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>creativity on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/tags/creativity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in creativity on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OT301, the non-commercial community in the heart of gentrified Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-14-ot301/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-14-ot301/</guid>
      <description>OT301 is a cultural hotspot in Amsterdam. Questioning its narrative as an autonomous space; we tried to engage with OT301’s history and the current state of affairs.
 Back in the ’80s, the lack of affordable housing helped the squatting movement to emerge in the Netherlands. ‘Squatting’ is what most would describe as occupying, living, in an abandoned building; not just out of necessity, but as a conscious political act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taste Before You Waste, soul food in Amsterdam Oost</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-02-taste-before-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-05-02-taste-before-en/</guid>
      <description>Photo Credits: Taste Before You Waste
The coronavirus pandemic will bring an additional 130 million people to starvation, the UN warned in late April. Meanwhile, Europe and the United States are producing unprecedented amounts of food waste following the abrupt decline in demand from restaurants, catering services and school mensas. The message here is that the food system in the western world is ridiculously toxic and wasteful. While others starve, “over 1/3 of all food produced globally is thrown away and in countries like the US, 50% of the food produced is wasted,” explains Isabel Allen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printed and rebel, Amsterdam’s zine scene survives hipsters and tourists</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-02-22-printed-and-rebel-en/</guid>
      <description>Photo via: Wikimedia, Author Lindsay Eyink, Licence CC BY 2.0
Wikimedia&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Author: W &amp;nbsp; CC BY 2.0 Lindsay Eyink&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Licence&amp;nbsp; --  Who would ever expect to find an anarchist bookshop in Jodenbreestraat Street, one of the most touristic spots of the capital? And yet there stands Fort of Sjakoo, one of the eldest stores of its kind, packed with shelves full of anarchist, feminist and left-wing political publications; the thoughts of some of the most important thinkers of history lay in ancient books, waiting to be read.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>