<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>climate justice on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/tags/climate-justice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in climate justice on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/tags/climate-justice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Rebellion a Pandam: il Covid non è “miracolo” per l’ambiente. Sfida ecologica ancora nelle nostre mani</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/posts/2020-04-28-extinction-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/posts/2020-04-28-extinction-it/</guid>
      <description>Tradotto dall’inglese
pics credit: XR, Sam ten Thij en Teresa, Extinction Rebellion NL
 Mentre il mondo muove i primi passi dal blocco, un aspetto sta diventando sempre più chiaro: dobbiamo ripensare le nostre interazioni sociali, il modo in cui sceglieremo di gestire il nostro ambiente in futuro, così come i nostri valori. A questo proposito, l’attuale crisi COVID-19 potrebbe offrire una finestra unica di opportunità per imparare e riflettere su questioni fondamentali.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Rebellion to Pandam: Covid is not a “blessing” for the environment. The future of the planet is still in our hands</title>
      <link>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/posts/2020-04-28-extinction-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estherkim99.github.io/pandam/posts/2020-04-28-extinction-en/</guid>
      <description>Italian Translation
pics credit: XR, Sam ten Thij en Teresa, Extinction Rebellion NL
 As the world slowly takes its first steps out of lockdown one aspect is becoming increasingly clear: we need to re-think our social interactions, the way we will manage our environment in the future, and above all the way we define human values. The current COVID-19 crisis might offer a unique perspective to learn from. The current debate seems to focus around how we can regain the status quo and return to our old lifestyle – “once all of this will be over“.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>