<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>homelessness on PanDam Amsterdam</title>
    <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/tags/homelessness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in homelessness on PanDam Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/tags/homelessness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Racism, ripoffs and ruthless landlords: housing market in Amsterdam is a nightmare</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-21-racism-ripoff-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-21-racism-ripoff-en/</guid>
      <description>Numbers released by Statistics Netherlands revealed that, in 2018, the number of foreigners who registered at a Dutch municipality exceeded the number of people who left by 69.5 thousand. In 2018, between January and March, 186 thousand immigrants moved to the Netherlands; 4.5k more than during the same period in 2017. Amsterdam is known to be a truly liberal city, tolerant, welcoming and with a high quality of life that is why the number of foreigners settling here is not likely to decrease anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truffe, razzismo e proprietari senza scrupoli: cercare casa ad Amsterdam è un incubo</title>
      <link>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-21-racism-ripoff-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pandam-magazine.herokuapp.com/posts/2020-03-21-racism-ripoff-it/</guid>
      <description>Tradotto dall’inglese
 Secondo CBS, l’Ufficio Statistico olandese, nel 2018, il numero di stranieri che si sono registrati in un comune dei Paesi Bassi ha superato il numero di coloro che se ne sono andati. Nel 2018, tra gennaio e marzo, 186 mila immigrati si sono trasferiti nei Olanda; 4,5k in più rispetto allo stesso periodo del 2017. Amsterdam nota per essere una città liberale, tollerante, accogliente e con un’alta qualità della vita, motivo per cui il numero di stranieri che si stabiliscono qui non è destinato a diminuire .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>